

# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- GIT
- Google Chrome developer tools
- Writing bug reports, checklists and test plans
- Adobe Photoshop / Figma
- Adaptive and cross-browser layout
- SEO
- Writing technical specifications
- Trello / Jira / Slack
- Google Analytics / Ads
- SMM

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Responsibility
- Critical Thinking
- Analysis
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Fast learner

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English (Intermediate / B1)
- Russian (Advanced / C1)
- Ukrainian (Proficiency / C2)

#### **CONTSCTS:**









Linkedin



# **Dmitry Lobachevsky**

# **Junior Project Manager**

Kyiv, Ukraine | 25 y.o.

750\$

### **ABOUT ME:**

Hey!

My name is Dmitry, I am the Project Manager.

I started learning HTML / CSS through video tutorials and online courses.

I got most of my knowledge from self-education and practical experience.

In the last places of work, I held the position of PM, my team consisted of 6+ people.

My experience as a project manager is 1+ year.

I always try to develop and improve my skills. I am looking for interesting projects and is open to any cooperation and communication.

Why Project Manager?

Because I enjoy my work, creating cool projects and leading the team!

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Quality Control Manager / Project Manager**

**EVERAD** 

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

- Setting goals
- Monitoring team work and completing tasks on time
- Quality control of products in accordance with technical documentation
- Preparation of reports for a week / month

#### Webmaster

#### **UAMADE STORE**

OCT 2019 - JUL 2021

- Adaptive and cross-browser layout
- Layout on CMS
- Administrative support for 3 sites
- Making SEO edits
- Filling the site with content
- Writing technical specifications
- Testing of web products.
- Writing bug reports, checklists and test cases
- Setting tasks for programmers, content maker, SEO and work control
- Promotion and collection of analytics

#### Restaurant manager

TENNESSEE RESTAURANT JUN 2019 - SEP 2019

- Control of staff work
- Resolving conflict situations
- Registration of supplies
- Restaurant Proceedings Report
- Interviewing candidates



# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- GIT
- Google Chrome developer tools
- Writing bug reports, checklists and test plans
- Adobe Photoshop / Figma
- Adaptive and cross-browser layout
- SEO
- Writing technical specifications
- Trello / Jira / Slack
- Google Analytics / Ads
- SMM

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Responsibility
- Critical Thinking
- Analysis
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Fast learner

## **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

- English (Intermediate / B1)
- Russian (Advanced / C1)
- Ukrainian (Proficiency / C2)

#### **CONTSCTS:**



+380 (99) 463 41 39



dmitryielail@gmail.com



**Telegram** 



Instagram



Linkedin



#### **EDUCATION**

#### Ucode

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Year of completion 2021

National University of Food Technologies (Kiev) **BACHELOR OF HOTEL AND RESTAURANT BUSINESS** Year of completion 2018

College of Economics and Law (Kiev) **CATERING BUSINESS** 

Year of completion 2015

#### **CONTACT US FOR A RECOMMENDATION**

Yaroslav Kozik **EVERAD** 

+380(96)177-26-56

TΧ